The Rubicon is a river near the city of Rome.
Thank you.
And when you cross the Rubicon, it's like saying you've passed the point of no return.
You're here to throw hands.
Right.
So because people hear that phrase, they don't know what it means.
And when you say that, that's what it means.
So now you know what it means.
Okay, we're back.
So, I mean, I think that that is a perfect example of what would be seen as fascism, whereas we see it now.
Look, I understand that people really, really like to stick to their sides in politics.
But I have seen Republicans push fascism.
I've seen Democrats push fascism.
And that is the ultimate control of the state.
For example, Republicans pushed fascism.
Now they have a convenient, forgetful memory, right?
Because they've all gotten behind Trump, who said that he was against the Iraq War.
But I haven't forgot how those people in the conservative movement rubbed their p*** to dead children for 15 years in Iraq and Afghanistan.
You cheered the murder of those people.
I watched you on television.
I read your comments.